This is a time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Maki D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is a sight!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
In an attempt to rescue his brother Ace,
Luffy enlisted the aid of the pirate empress, Boa Hancock,
to sneak onto a Navy vessel bound for Impel Down.
I'm sure you heard about what your brother's been up to.
Now, I don't expect us to get along perfect,
but challenging the world government head-on and wrecking up Eni's lobby is over the line.
Oh, by the way, I told the little punk about his father.
Of course, the news took him by surprise.
Can't blame the boy.
Our fathers.
To hell with them.
And to hell with you if you ever thought we could be Marines.
We've both got the blood of criminals flowing through our veins.
And that was the only gift those bastards ever gave us.
I took the name Portgus from my mother because I owe her so much.
But I don't owe my father a damned thing.
I don't even remember the bastard.
He can keep his name.
I know, I know.
But the man tried.
He wanted to...
Enough, all right!
Listen to me.
Don't fight it.
Run wild.
With us, our flag will be yours.
And I will call you my son.
Whitebeard is my only father.
Got it, old man.
Better for us to quit while we're still ahead.
Bucky the Clown had a good run.
But I'm afraid his luck as a pirate has run out.
No!
I refuse to accept it.
He's a man among men.
The only way Captain Buggy can go out is in a blaze of glory.
All right.
Impel down.
This is it.
Welcome to my prison.
Impel down.
Oops, jumped the gun there.
It's not, well, exactly mine just yet.
I'm the Vice Warden here, Hannibal.
Well, for now at least.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Vice Admiral.
Oh, and don't forget these.
Keep in mind that they're sea prism stone.
You call me a visitor here, not a prisoner.
Then you put me in those?
Countdown to Ace's execution.
Thirty-three hours.
A reunion in hell?
The man who ate the chop-chop fruit.
You'd leave me powerless?
How cruel.
But necessary.
The man who ate the chop-chop fruit.
Be gentle, I'm delicate.
What happened?
It's safe now, Luffy.
Wow, that was close.
I was starting to think I'd just have to crawl out from there like a cockroach and hope for the best.
That power of yours is really handy in a pinch, huh?
Even so, I'm afraid that this is as far as I'll be able to accompany you.
They're quite insistent on placing me in those sea prism stone handcuffs.
And once they take my cloak, you'll have nowhere to hide.
I just wish... I wish I could do more to help you, but...
Aw, don't talk like that.
You got me in this place, didn't you?
That's more than I could have done alone.
Even though there's guards everywhere, we made it all this way, no problem.
I can handle the rest.
Luffy.
Breaking your brother out will be challenging enough, but if you get captured as well,
who knows what horrors you might face.
One wrong step and you may never see the light of day again.
I know you want to save Ace, but this is dangerous.
Please, take care of yourself, too.
I won't let you down, you have my word.
Thanks for everything, Hancock, you're the best.
I won't forget what you've done, not for the rest of my life.
He just called me by my name.
My real, actual name.
For the first time.
Cool, whatever works for you, Hammock.
Can I get seconds over here, Hammock?
Hey, Hammock, what are you doing?
Hey, Hancock.
My life is finally complete.
I can die happy.
Hey, you can turn that lady back now.
I should be fine up here.
Say it, Luffy.
Say my name again.
Uh, what?
This is taking too long.
This situation is unprecedented.
She's probably just being thorough.
Huh.
Heh.
A thorough body search.
Hm.
Ah!
Oh, that's so naughty!
Get your mind out of the gutter, damn it!
Uh, Vice Warden Hannibal, we're not getting any visuals from the surveillance nail in the examination room.
Is there something going on in there we don't know about?
Huh?
Domino, something wrong in there?
No answer, huh?
It's okay.
I'm the Vice Warden, right?
Checking things out in there is strictly business, you see?
Even if that business happens to involve two hot chicks touching each other!
Ugh.
Huh?
Hm.
We have completed the body search, sir.
Ugh.
Beep, beep.
Scratch that last report.
Everything is fine here.
I hope I didn't cause a problem, sir.
Did the exam take too long?
Huh?
No.
Everything's fine on our end, too.
I see that your guests are treated as poorly as your prisoners here.
Surely an Empress deserves better than this.
It is a pity.
But in Impel Down, we can't afford to make exceptions to the rules.
I wonder why I can't shake this strange feeling.
Lead the way.
Ah, yes.
If you'll let me in front, please.
Or just go that way.
Before we visit Ace, we'll take this elevator to what we call the Burning Heat Floor,
where we'll stop by the Warden Magellan's office.
Fair warning, as the name implies, it's quite hot there.
Luffy.
Be bold, but be safe.
Bye, Encom.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
Hancock, I love you.
Oh, he really does love me.
He's Empress Hancock.
What's wrong?
Do you need mouth to mouth?
Are you ill?
You were fine just a moment ago.
What happened?
Okay, not sure where to take things from here.
Hancock said Ace is probably underwater.
Looks like that elevator might head down a long way.
Oh, yeah.
The fever cart might come in handy.
Looks like they grabbed dinner, too.
Open the hatch.
Nice work.
Get it to the fridge and we'll be done.
Hope you're feeling better, Empress.
We should be passing through level one any second now.
Let me out of here, dammit!
It's even worse than I expected.
Surely dust.
This floor hosts relatively minor offenders, so these whippings are mostly a formality.
Madness.
Yes, and yet it's the truth.
Level one of Impel Down is known as the Crimson Floor, by the way.
What's crimson about it?
That would be a secret.
Level two is the floor of wild beasts from hell.
Pretty straightforward.
As we move deeper underwater, we reach level three, the starvation floor.
Followed by level four, the burning heat floor, which is our destination.
You can't tell from the surface, but this structure is actually quite expansive.
Since it takes a while for this elevator to get to level four, you'll have plenty of time
to indulge in the cacophony of screams.
And is Fire Fist Ace on level four?
No, and that isn't the bottom floor, either.
We have a wide selection of torturous...
Luffy.
He should be down these stairs somewhere.
No fair, you cheater!
We thought you were just a clown.
You didn't tell us you could do that?
Can it, would you?
The real clowns here are you losers.
Getting whipped like dogs every damn day.
Of course I'm going to break out the first chance I get.
Are you just going to run out on us?
Huh?
That sounds like something a friend would say, and you folks are no friends of mine.
I'm a free eagle chump, so deal with it.
If you don't like being in there, why don't you slip out like me?
What's that you can't?
Well, I guess you're just going to have to die, huh?
Kiss my ass, Thomas!
Come on!
You won't get away with this.
Funky!
I'm getting away just fine!
A surveillance transponder snail?
A surveillance transponder snail!
Eeeeeeeeeuuuuuuuuuuuhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Hi fellas.
We found him! That's Buggy the Clown, prisoner from level 1, Community Cell Number 4.
He's in the hallway in front of solitary cell number 22.
Grab him and quit!
Gah, damn it. Stupid snail! This is all your fault!
The transponder snail 71 has been shut off!
You blew it Buggy old pal.
Don't come crying to us when they're torturing you to death.
Serves you right, you dummy.
Yeah, he'll wish he was dead for sure.
Here come the Lugoni.
Happy hunting.
Make him suffer.
The fever card keeps leading me down, but now what?
Guess I'm out of stairs.
All right, men. We're looking for prisoner 8,200.
What? The stupid clown?
No one knew he had devil fruit powers. You got the handcuffs?
Yeah, we're good.
Let's move.
Spread up and flank him.
Cool. I made it.
Hurry!
Wonder what's up.
So all of these are prison cells?
What's that?
I gotta get moving.
Go away, you bunch of jerks!
Have mercy on me!
This way!
Go on.
Huh? Danger.
It already has a skull. Who's gonna press it?
Oh, jeez.
That was close.
Why did the traps go off?
Hey! The trap's activated over there! Surround the hallway!
Crap! The guards are coming!
Halt!
They're gone!
That was lucky.
Huh?
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Buddy, slow down. Hold on a second.
Kind of busy.
Yeah, that's what it looks like, but how the heck did you get out of your cell?
Hey, what's going on?
I didn't get out. I came in from the outside.
Well, bye!
Hey, hold up! There's no way that's the truth!
Uh-huh, it's so true.
You don't look like a jailer.
So who are you and why the hell are you here?
He's not behind bars, so maybe it's true.
You guys have some really bad attitudes.
Wait a sec. Any of you know where I can find Ace?
Uh, Ace? Wait, Ace? You mean him? The guy on death row?
That's the one. I came here to bust him out of this place.
Yeah, good luck with that.
We don't get a lot of info down here, but I heard they just brought him in.
If that's true and he is here, then he's got to be on level five.
No way you're getting down there. You're screwed, pal.
That's the floor where they hold all the prisoners with a bounty of a hundred million or more.
Level five, huh?
Oh, and by the way, pal, why you're here, you think you could run to the jailer's room and pick us up some keys?
Yeah, buddy. Wouldn't be no trouble, right?
This has got to be destiny, man. I mean, what else would bring us together like this?
It's like you were born to set us free, right?
What are those things?
Stop looking forwarding!
I don't like them!
Run! Homie, they're gonna kill you!
Hurry! We're taking them back! I like you!
Right side! And left side!
You're dying!
How you like that, suckers?
You can cut me all you want! I ain't the chop-chop fruit!
Straw rats!
What the hell are you doing here?
Oh, buggy.
Ah! Thanks for reminding me why I hate you!
I see prison hasn't made you any less annoying.
Speaking of, guess that King of the Pirates thing ain't working out too well.
I came here on my own.
Only dumb people like you get caught and thrown in jail.
Say what?
You threw yourself in jail and you're calling me the dumb one?
You must have known I was here.
That's the real reason you broke in, isn't it?
To save me?
I'm not into you, weirdo!
Just shut up and get the hell out of my way!
I told Hancock I'd take care of myself
and you got all these stupid axe monkeys chasing after me!
Oh! I see! This is all about you, is it?
Stop touching me, you clown!
No!
This is supposed to be a cinch!
I called it Buggy's peaceful escape plan!
Does this look peaceful to you?
Who cares?
They're surrounding us, damn it!
I hate this!
Hey, shouldn't we just beat those things up?
Easy for you to say you haven't been tortured.
Oh, how my delicate body has suffered
from the blows of these monsters.
Why do you think I'm running away in the first place?
Yeah, but I wasn't planning to lose.
Right, clearly you thought this out.
I'm on a mission here.
My cover's already been blown,
so I gotta get this done in a hurry.
You know, that's the number one reason
why I hate you and that redhead so much.
Both of you are always so optimistic
in the worst way possible.
All right, fine.
I'll go along with your crazy plan.
It's not like I have a choice!
Time for my specialty!
Causing chaos!
Works for me!
After forming an unlikely alliance,
Muffy is able to race through Impel Down
thanks to the help of Buggy's chop-chop powers.
However, when they make their way
to what is known as the Crimson Hell,
they discover their descent
will not be as swift as it foresees.
On the next One Piece,
Breakthrough the Crimson Hell,
Buggy's chaos-inducing plan,
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!